{
    "subject": "resource/Don_Davis_(composer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1957-02-04",
    "human_readable": "Don Davis (composer) was born on February 4, 1957.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.840035617351532,
            "question": "When was Don Davis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7306694388389587,
            "question": "Where was Don Davis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7228160500526428,
            "question": "In what year did Don Davis begin his career as a composer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6118225455284119,
            "question": "Which genres of music has Don Davis composed in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5969902873039246,
            "question": "What is Don Davis known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3887844681739807,
            "question": "Has Don Davis won any awards for his compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33907365798950195,
            "question": "Who are some of Don Davis's collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3376738131046295,
            "question": "Is there a particular instrument that Don Davis specializes in playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3069112002849579,
            "question": "What influences Don Davis's musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2818131744861603,
            "question": "What are some of Don Davis's most famous works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Don Davis (composer) was born on February 4, 1957.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4973_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What influences Don Davis's musical style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4973_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a particular instrument that Don Davis specializes in playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4973_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Don Davis's collaborators?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4973_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4973_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Don Davis was indeed born on February 4, 1957."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}